http://www.everygeneration.co.uk/index.php/privacy-policy

Every Generation Media - Privacy Policy
Login/Out
Search...
Every Generation Media
About UsEGM TimelineSocial PolicyWhy is the census importantMental Well Being & BHM25 years of Black Political RepresentationPublishingFilmsIntergenerational LearningConsultancy & WorkshopsSponsorship & DonationGenealogyAlex Haley - RootsGenealogy BooksFamily History Case StudiesMotherland Case StudyDiaspora Family HistoryTracing Your Family HeritageGenealogy Web ResourcesBlack British History100 Great Black Britons100 Great Black Britons Book100 Great Black Britons CampaignAward Walter Tull the Military Cross100 Great Black Britons Book 2020Windrush GenerationThe Windrush Generation LegacyA Charmed Life : Eddie Martin NobleCalls for Annual Windrush DayBHM Black History MonthBlack History Month - OriginsAkyaaba Addai-Sebo InterviewEphemeraBlack RetroConsultancy and WorkshopsSponsorshipShop
You are here: HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Details
Category: Terms & Conditions
1. General
Every Generation Media Limited (referred to in this policy as "Every Generation Media" or "we" or "our") is the owner of this website:everygeneration.co.uk ("Website"). Every Generation Media''s privacy policy is set out below. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you via the Website. Please read this policy carefully. By using the Website or any of the services we provide via the Website, you agree to bound by the terms of this policy in respect of information collected about you via the Website.
If you are under 12, please do not submit any of your personal details online to us or by using our services such as our message/notice boards or chat rooms unless your parent or guardian has provided us with their written permission. If you are under 12 and would like to ask us a question or use any of our services which involves providing any of your personal information, please ask your parent or guardian to send a letter giving their permission. We will then take any action we deem necessary to verify the permission. We reserve the right to reject any letters which we do not believe to be authentic. Personal information means any information from which you can be identified such as your name, your e-mail address or your photograph.
2. Personal Information Collected. 2.1. We collect information from you which is necessary to provide you with services via this Website. Certain services can only be accessed if you are a registered user. We also collect information from you when you complete any forms on this Website. The information we collect from you may include: (i) name, user name, password, mother''s maiden name (ii) e-mail address, postal address, telephone number
2.2. You do not have to give us any personal information, however you may not be able to access the full range of services we provide via the Website if you do not provide your personal information.
3. Use of Your Personal Information 3.1. We will use your personal information in order to: (i) provide you with services via the Website (ii) send you information about our products and services and our newsletter (iii) verify your identity
3.2. We may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of a sale of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganisation.
3.3 Other than set out above, we will not disclose any of your personal information without your permission unless we are required by law to do so (for example, if required to do so by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime).
4. Information Automatically Collected From Your Computer 4.1 When you visit our Website our web server automatically records your IP address. This IP address is not linked to any of your personal information.
4.2 We may also gather other non-personal information (from which we cannot identify you) such as the type of your internet browser which we use to provide you with a more effective service.
5. Cookies 5.1 We do not use cookies.
5.2 Our Website may have third party advertisements. Cookies may be associated with these advertisements so that the advertiser can track users in relation to their advertisements. We do not have any control or access to these third party cookies.
6.Information about other products and services From time to time we may send you information about our products and services which may be of interest to you but only if you have given us permission to do so. You can tell us to stop this at anytime by completing our feedback form.
7. Changes to Your Details If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied to us, please contact us as set out below.
8. Use of Forums or Chat Rooms The Website may from time to time include chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups on which you can post information. Any information that you post in these areas becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal details as part of this information.
9. Security We have implemented technology and policies to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use.
10. Third Party Links We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if you have access to them using links from our Website and recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.
11. Transferring Your Information Outside Europe 11.1 As part of the services we provide via our Website, the information provided to us may be transferred outside of the European Union ("EU"). For example one of our service providers may be outside of the EU or our servers may be located in a country outside of the EU . If we transfer your information outside of the EU in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this privacy policy.
11.2 If you use any of our services whilst outside of the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide those services.
12. Feedback and Complaints If you have any questions or comments about privacy issues, or if you have a complaint about how we are using your personal information, then contact us via our feedback form, or write to us at Every Generation Media Limited, Unit 104 Coppergate House, 16 Brune Street, London E1 7NJ.
Main Menu
HomeIndependence & EmancipationHeritage EducationEvent ListingsCalendarWeb LinksRSS links
Patrick Vernon & the Ubele Initiative Launch Covid-19 Bereavement Fund
Copyright © 2013 Every Generation Media. All Rights Reserved.
Site Design DestaNation
